a quote that the guy who put together
the intellectual dark website use at the
top of one of his pages was when two or
three gather in my name I am there with
them and it was a biblical quote yeah
and I was very struck by that it really
fits with what you were saying about
there's a sense of something good
happening when when these people get
together and talk in this way yes I
think this is right and I think it's
deep which is to say that well let me
use maybe Peterson's framework just to
make it soft wicker self-reflective it
seems to me that there is something that
happens when two or more gathered
together in my name and oftentimes in
history we've needed that something to
make it and the situation was not easy
the situation was complex challenging
and so it required that something that
whatever it is that happens when we are
gathered together in a space of well
collaboration let's just make it again
very simple a space of peace a space of
mutual understanding not for the purpose
of delivering on the same opinion but
really for going deep and trying to find
something which is trying to frankly
express itself like to listen and so if
that story the story that I just told is
true then it would be in our bones it
would be in our deepest mythology and
our deepest traditions I do use religion
that this is the place to go that when
trouble is brewing gather together
answer into this space this is where we
do these sorts of things this is how we
solve these kinds of problems